[Music]
Hello everyone, my name is Onet and
today I'm going to talk to you about how
to migrate uh record links and nodes
from your on premise database to your
cloud instance.
Um what are record links? First of
foremost uh record links and nodes are
very critical. Uh they can contain
customer insights, annotations or
references and they are important for
your day-to-day decisions making.
Previously record links and not notes
were not migrated from on-rem database
to cloud. Uh so partners would have to
spend a lot of time and effort to bring
them over. But now with new capabilities
record links and nodes migration is part
of the cloud migration process. So the
teams can uh retain the narrative of
their business process even if they
transition to the cloud. Let's see how
that looks.
So I have set up cloud migration and ran
data replication. I can check the cloud
migration management page and see the
status. You can see the replication was
completed successfully. Replications
will bring bring the uh record links and
nodes to a buffer table so that we don't
override your existing record links and
notes. What you'll need to do is hit
this action
migrate record links and notes in order
to bring them from the buffer table to
your to the actual table. You'll notice
this uh new field called warnings and I
just have one. It will tell you that
record link table has not been migrated
since the last replication. So we warn
you about it that you don't forget.
Let's look at customers for example.
I've got one customer here that uh I had
record links and notes in my onrem
database but is not here yet. So what
I'll just do is go ahead and run this
action migrate record links and notes.
You can see the warning went away and if
I check the customer now
you see that the links and the notes are
here.
So that's it. That's how easy it is.
just uh some couple of notes that I
would like to run by before I say
goodbye. Make sure you run the record
links and notes migration after the
replication so that records are moved to
the buffer table beforehand.
Also, make sure you do this uh before
doing the uh user mapping because when
you do the user mapping uh we'll change
the records uh on the users on the
record links and notes uh to the ones
that you map to.
And just so you know, we do not
overwrite your existing record links and
notes. So it's very safe to use. You can
run it the run the action multiple
times.
That's it. If you want to learn more,
check out uh this resources. Um thank
you for listening.